<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>The Attention Revolution Will Be Tokenized</description>
    <link>http://www.ourket.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.ourket.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:00:41 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:00:41 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Ourket - Ourcoin</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;100% Profits Direct From Online Advertisers Anonymously&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;From Online Slave, To Owning the Internet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;gm-anon-retail-frens-this-is-for-you&quot;&gt;gm anon retail frens, this is for you.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Banks controlled the physical financial system. Off of Our Trust&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Websites controlled the digital internet system.  Off of Our Attention&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13 years ago to the day, the white paper which solves the former was released.  Today, on October 31, 2021 - We release the white paper for Ourket, which solves the latter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-do-online-platform-websites-collectively-worth-trillions-of-dollars-make-all-of-their-money&quot;&gt;How do online platform websites, collectively worth Trillions of dollars, make all of their money?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quite simple Really&lt;br /&gt;
From Your Attention - From All of Our Collective Attention&lt;br /&gt;
Paid to them from the companies who pay them handsomely to place their advertisements on their website(s).  Which You Are The Product.  These websites are the gatekeepers of the internet profit railroad.  Attention and Data are the financial coal running these multi-billion dollar website trains.  Their only business model is to monetize your attention. Monetize your data.  Using high level psychological manipulation, strategic dopamine drops and dirty backhanded tricks, all in the effort to keep you viewing more of their advertisements and returning to their website more often. Using human psychology, our data and shady tactics against us, all to benefit them, their bottom lines and make them and their small controlled group of investors - more cash.  Not one ounce of care provided for Our Well-being or to benefit the everyday user of the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is well documented. And for most of society, not a closed door secret.&lt;br /&gt;
But how did this come to be?  And what is the answer?&lt;br /&gt;
Businesses advertise, they have done so since the foundation of media.  They will continue to do so for as long as there is a medium for them to communicate their message to current and new customers.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Free World Capitalism.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
And they are willing to pay to advertise, and willing to pay well.  They know their message is a distraction. They know they are an interruption to Our current broadcasting message.  But they take the risk and pay money, in the hopes they can try to offer, sell or update us on their newest products or services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only option until today, for big and small businesses alike, is to pay the platforms who provide the websites, not us directly.  And since the creation of the internet, the companies’ only choice was to pay the piper and use the good ol’boy profiteering cabal network.  Middlemen, who manipulate and monetize Us.  Our data.  Our emotions.  Our Attention.  For Profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over time, or very well since in the very beginning, this is how online marketing profits have been controlled and manipulated.  Making Absolute Certain they always Cheat the Game. And We Continue to Lose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hello-ourket&quot;&gt;Hello Ourket&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Web3.0 in its simplest form, is removing the middleman from the internet.&lt;br /&gt;
What if…  You could have a direct relationship, privately and as anonymously as you choose, with these companies directly, who want to show you their advertisements; Who also would rather deal with you directly anyway.  Additionally every time you viewed (not clicked) or watched or clicked their Advertisements, You Now Get Paid 100% of the Profits - Directly From Them, Anonymously.  For Free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Ourket’s Own, First to Market, Full-Circle Digitized Token - OurCoin.&lt;br /&gt;
Ourket’s software dev is fully decentralized and open sourced to the community.  A dev community who will be rewarded in building Ourket’s solution from the ground up.  Combined with a true grass roots retail focused digital token release of OurCoin.  No VCs, No Insider’s, No Whale’s have invested one cent, or will be given backdoor access to tokens to benefit them, and screw over You.  Zero special offerings have been made and absolutely no tokens held back for anyone except the 2 creators.  This we believe, is the fairest way possible to give retail the best chance of success, and in our opinion, the true definition of Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those who believe the earliest, will be rewarded the most.  But as the Ourket community grows, the more collective power we will all gain together as a community.  The Attention Revolution will be for all of us.  As every person across the globe who downloads Ad Replacement or Blocking Software powered by Ourket Technology will regain the reins of their Attention back, and will receive OurCoins directly from the Advetisers as they surf the Web.  We who see this vision from the beginning, through the bull and bear markets, who work together, but independently and anonymously will build this reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Ourket receives massive implementation, will the creators make money? Yes. Again, Free World Capitalism.  But not at the expense of the community, or the core concept of Ourket’s ideal, that your attention is yours.  And you will receive 100% of every dollar created from your own Attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be no rug on our end, as we release it all to You.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will be You who will form and transform the movement; Not the Crypto and Silicon VC crews which have not an honest care in the world for your well-being.  They have enough. And We have had enough.  The Ourket community will not just be investing fiat, or technological experience, or time, or social capital, when letting the unaware person, there is a better way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will invest something, in our opinion, worth way more… Investing Faith.  Faith we can all work together and reclaim ownership of what was ours to begin with.  We will all reap the rewards of real evolutionary change.  Not a VC Insider securing 100x lockup regardless if everyone else loses their backside.  Not the fat cat website cabal.  Not the system which has been pitted against us from the very creation of the internet, manipulating our data and emotions for their profit motive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Attention Revolution OurFrens&lt;br /&gt;
Where We All Win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Source&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Decentralized&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Crypto Currency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Web 3.0&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Future Verse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They all have their core meanings, definitions and place in the new digital landscape which is currently being created from the ground up.  For the purest in each category, they even have a tough time collectively defining what each means at their core.  It is not up to Ourket to solve this debate.  They will be debated and solved by their own communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we present is the core use-case for Ourket, and for us, it is simple in design and application.  Replace the Ads you see online, which before now, were controlled by the profiteering cabal.  And give 100% back to each and every person worldwide who downloads Ourket’s free application.  We confidently believe Ourket will be developed and a global attention revolution will be achieved through the implementation of OurCoin, Ourket’s own revolutionary token.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ourcoin-is-the-first-full-circle-️-use-case-for-digital-tokensation&quot;&gt;OurCoin is the first full circle ⭕️ use case for digital tokensation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OurCoin will be backed not by hype or speculation, but by the annual 500 billion dollar market, established and as old as the internet itself; Online/Digital Advertising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;starting-the-circle&quot;&gt;“Starting The Circle”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advertisers/Companies use their fiat currency to purchase OurCoin tokens.  Using OurCoin, they can now purchase your attention through Ourket’s technology by funding a pool dedicated to payouts for an advertisement.  In effect, purchasing ads on the Network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;finishing-the-circle&quot;&gt;“Finishing The Circle”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once an Ad is viewed, clicked on, or watched, the full amount of OurCoin that was paid to show you the ad, will be seamlessly and directly transferred to your private token wallet.  Allowing you the hodl, trade for other tokens, or convert earned OurCoin to the Fiat currency of your choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;token-distribution&quot;&gt;Token Distribution&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;9% collectively go to the 2 creators. 
(which will be worth absolutely zero, if grass roots community does not think they have value.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;18% will be placed in a defi fund to be annually utilized for the Devs and R&amp;amp;D to continue to update the software and backend updates.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3% placed in a non-profit DAO defi fund to support the Apes. https://www.janegoodall.org&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3% placed in a daily rolling defi fund lottery to be distributed to the Ourket community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kadena-blockchain&quot;&gt;Kadena Blockchain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outket will be built on Kadena for 5 simple, as well as critical, reasons; Safety, Speed, Gas, Fair Tokenization and an overall Belief in the foundation’s core thesis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to process millions (or billions) of online internet advertisement transaction between the advertiser and you, the speed and security of digital banking is necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cost per transaction, even for CPM (cost per thousand) impressions (an ad which is just shown on your screen, not clicked on) requires a fee (gas) low enough to not only support 1st world pricing but also Our Frens across the globe where advertising prices are a fraction of Tier 1 markets.  Providing every member of the Ourket community around the world the highest value for their attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kadena’s layer 1 PoW, fair token distribution and thoughtful executive decision to not be a pawn to the VC cartel, stands shoulder to shoulder with Ourket’s core beliefs and is a partnership we are confident is in the best interest of Our Community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;thesis&quot;&gt;Thesis&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Vision of Ourket’s ad replacing/filtering technology will be built and achieved by all of us.  Those of you, wherever you are in the world, who recognize the problem, and can develop the solution or take part by saying no to the current paradigm.  Ourket’s entry will be fully open source and built off of current ad-blocking technology.  Instead of blocking the advertisements, they will now be replaced. And will now pay all of you, for all of it.  Paid in OurCoin.  Which will be Fairly divided among the creators, the retail investors, dev creators, Ourket’s own members, and the Apes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To our knowledge, No concept has achieved this. Especially at scale, globally, backed by decades old, established, and ripe for a takeover marketplace, worth Trillions of Dollars every few years.  We call on anyone who receives this message, with an understanding of what we are building, to assist. You are welcome here and We ask for your help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;wagmi&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 16:40:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.ourket.com/2021/10/31/ourcoin-launch-whitepaper/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.ourket.com/2021/10/31/ourcoin-launch-whitepaper/</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
